# Laura E. Green

Email: GreenLaE@outlook.com | Phone: 571-594-6931 | Tucson, AZ 85719

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/laura-g-086284171

Github: MechanicalMouse | Website: mechanicalmouse.github.io

#### **SUMMARY**

Web developer with over 8 years of basic forum-based HTML and CSS experience. Continually refining skills in front-end JavaScript, Node.js, and more. Passionate learner, problem solver, and creative thinker. Organized, patient, and driven to ensure high-quality work.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

CSS, SASS, HTML5, Node.js, JavaScript

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Find-A-Recipe

|github.com/MechanicalMouse/Find-A-Recipe |mechanicalmouse.github.io/Find-A-Recipe/

**Front-End Developer** 

- Helps in finding a recipe, either with the recipe name or a chosen list of ingredients.
- Used Bootstrap and SASS

## **Gem Game**

|github.com/MechanicalMouse/Gem-Game |mechanicalmouse.github.io/Gem-Game/ Front-End Developer

- A simple click game. Use mystery value gems to reach the goal number.
- Used JavaScript, CSS, and HTML

## **Hamster Trivia**

|github.com/MechanicalMouse/TriviaGame |mechanicalmouse.github.io/TriviaGame/ Front-end Developer

- A short trivia game about Syrian hamsters.
- Used JavaScript, CSS, and HTML

# **EXPERIENCE**

Mturk Worker - Amazon Mechanical Turk - Tucson, AZ

2019 - Current

Answering surveys, recognizing bots, and labeling and categorizing images and data.

<u>Sewing Contractor</u> – *Arizona Apparel Manufacturing, LLC* – Tucson, AZ **2018** - **2018** 

Attached tabs to shoe covers as part of an assembly-line-type production system.

**Sabbatical** - 2016 - 2017

Took time out of work to care for a family member.

<u>Customer Sales Associate</u> – Walgreens – Fairfax, VA

2017 - 2017

Organized and restocked shelves and helped unload shipments.

#### **EDUCATION**

**University of Arizona**, Tucson, AZ – Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp